## **OLES GEDZ**

C++ DEVELOPER

Github:

https://github.com/olesgedz/

Email:

gedzoles@gmail.com

Phone:

+7(985) 948-98-42

**Profile** 

Age: 24 years

I am studying at School 42, a computer graphics course. I have experience in leading a team of five people. I strive to gain new knowledge and implement my skills.

Achievements

Computer graphics

Creating a graphical editor based on path tracing technology.

School 42

Creation of projects such as: Ray Tracer, Rasterizer, Raycaster engine, Voxel engine. Unity

IBM Fabric

- Participation in several projects of independent studios.

- Creation of a VR application for the practice of public speaking using data read from neural interfaces.

- Development of a VR platform for laboratory activities in university MEPhI.

Work experience

University MEPhI

Unity VR/AR Developer

2020 - present

School 42

2019 - present

Code Class

Programming C#, Unity and Mobile Development teacher As a result of the training: the students created games of different genres using Unity.

C#

MovieQuest

2014 - 2015

2017 - 2018

Electrcal engineer

Designer and responsible for the assembly and operation of the quest rooms. Designed and assembled three attractions.

Programming languages

C++Python

Technologies:

OpenCL Unity XR Docker Git OpenGL Unity Mars Oculus intergration

Threads SDL

Vulkan

C

Tensorflow

Education

School42 - **9.67** LVL

English - C2.

Incomplete higher education after two years of study at NUST MISIS, "Electronics and Nanomaterials".

Additional education Courses:

Participation in the HSE summer school "Цифровая трансформация благотворительного сектора"

Coursera C++ by Moscow Institute of Physics and Technology, Yandex & E-Learning Development Fund UC San DiegoX: CSE167x Computer Graphics by Ravi Ramamoorth Computer Graphics with Modern OpenGL and C++ by Ben Cook

 $\operatorname{Gedz} \operatorname{Oles} - \underline{\operatorname{gedzoles@gmail.com}} - + 7(985) \ 948 - 98 - 42$